(Howard:)What if they're women?
(Penny:)Stare at them
and make them feel uncomfortable.
[GUNSHOTS ON TV]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Hey.
- How's it going?
- Fine.
So listen, the Nuart is showing the revised,
definitive cut of Blade Runner.
- Seen it.
- No.
(Howard:)You've seen
the 25th Anniversary Final Cut.
(Howard:)This one has eight seconds
of previously-unseen footage.
(Howard:)They say it completely changes
the tone of the film.
(Leonard:)Pass.
Come on. Afterwards, there's a Q&A
with Harrison Ford's body double.
Look, I am in the "Halo" battle
of my life here.
(Leonard:)There's this kid in Copenhagen,
he has no immune system.
(Leonard:)So all he does is sit in his bubble
and play "Halo" 24/7.
(Howard:)Can't you play him some other time?
(Leonard:)Not if you believe his doctors.